Greetings Traveler!

I am pleased to offer this font that has been a labor of love to you.

This font is based on the title screen of the video game Stardew Valley, 
a wholesome farming/crafting type game that has a dedicated fan base.

The letters S-T-A-R-D-E-W-V-L-Y are based on the design of the Title, 
but all of the other capitals, including all of the lowercase letters, 
are of my design, in the style of the original letters. 
Symbols from the game are the stardrop which is an asterisk (*), 
and the coin/gold icon is the dotaccent (˙) for use above foreign letters.

If enough feedback and appreciation is offered, I may offer per request a 
dingbat/wingdings font based on all the icons, crops, etc from the game.

I have included the Leafy ALL Capitals font, 
the lowercase being the capitals from the "Stardew Valley Regular" font. 

The leaves of the S and W match the title screens letters, but V and Y 
do not match. This is because if you decide to mix and match capitals and 
lowercase (highly recommended) to create an interesting design, 
the side hanging leaves of V and W would interfere with the next 
letter before or after.

This font is not for unauthorized redistribution and is not to be made for sale. 

ConcernedApe is the creator and developer of the game Stardew Valley, and this font 
is solely an expansion of the title screen font.
 

The font is listed as donationware under DaFont because of the time dedicated to 
the creation of all the glyphs, but if your donation happens to come later or 
not at all, that is fine as well. Im glad youve downloaded it regardless! :)

If you do appreciate my specific efforts in regards to this reimagining of the 
Title Screen letters, you can donate by clicking the “donate to author” link 
underneath the download button of this font on Dafont.com, or to my Paypal using 
the email address EMTcomartist@aol.com. 

You can also offer feedback to that email as well. Feedback may include requests 
for letter or symbol redesign, requests for use of the font in endeavors beyond 
personal use (to be offered on a case by case basis), expressions of appreciation 
with screenshots and pictures of how you've used it, and things like these. 
Make sure the subject line reads “Stardew Valley Font Feedback” or 
“Stardew Valley Font Question”.

Thank you once again for downloading, and have fun!

Best wishes,

Eliot Truelove
